http://www.nbsoft.co.uk/privacy

Home -> Privacy Policy
Send
Privacy Policy
At nbsoft we respect your privacy, this privacy policy has been
written in as plain English as possible so everyone can understand what
information we collect and how we use it.
Information Handling
On this site we may collect a small amount of information regarding your computer specification such as the version of your operating system, please note that no personal information is collected and your privacy is our upmost concern, we do not disclose this information in any way to any
third party company's, organizations or people, it is for our own use
only. No human will see any of your passwords as this process is completely
automated, you are allowed to post comments wherever this option
is available. However we reserve the right to restrict access to these
parts if you fail to conform with the terms and conditions, we may block
these parts in any way we can to prevent access by that user again.
Information Storage/Cookies
We may store information on your computer in the form of 'Cookies',
these are small files that are stored onto your hard drive through your
browser and are designed to personalize your experience on our site,
this can only happen if your browser supports them and if they are
enabled. The type of information we store in the cookies are things such
as usernames and presets which you may activate around our site.
Thank you for taking time to read this privacy policy.
Legal
Privacy
About Us
© Copyright 2001-2020 nbsoft
